rewardsnetwork.com 2005-02-06

# Rewards Network - Privacy Policy

##### Our pledge to you, our member

Rewards Network Inc. and its affiliates (referred to herein as "we", "us" and "our") respect your privacy and know that you care how information about you is used and shared. We have prepared this detailed policy (this "Privacy Policy") because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make an informed decision about the extent of your use of our services, in particular your membership in our Rewards Network program (the "Rewards Network").

Simply put:  

  * We will not collect personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number (collectively, "Personal Information") from you or a third party without your knowledge and permission;
  * We will not disclose your Personal Information to non-affiliated third parties unless 1) You are part of a rewards or incentive program that gives you "miles", "points", cashback rewards, or other incentives for your eligible transactions at our participating merchants, in which case, we will share your Personal Information with the operator of the rewards or incentive program, or your credit card issuer, only to the extent necessary in order to enable them to credit your account with the reward earned. 2) You have requested that we book or make a reservation with one of our participating merchants on your behalf (for example, booking a hotel room, making a dinner reservation, or reserving a rental car) in which case we shall share your Personal Information with the participating merchant only to the extent necessary to enable them to accept or cancel your reservation;
  * We will allow you to view and access your Personal Information and other information associated with your registration either through our website, over the telephone or through a written request; and
  * We will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect from you.

##### Your Personal Information: what we collect and how we use it

We gather the following types of Personal Information in connection with the provision of our services to you.

  * When you just visit our web site: You can visit our site without revealing who you are or providing any Personal Information. When you visit our site we collect usage information ("session data"), but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We use session data to better understand things like how our site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at our site, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors, and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to our site. We use this information to improve our site content and ease of use. 
  * When you join and use the Rewards Network: If you decide to become a member of the Rewards Network, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share with us. The Personal Information that is collected is necessary for us to provide you with the benefits available to you as a member of the Rewards Network. This Personal Information includes things like your name, e-mail and mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, loyalty program numbers and the answer to a security question in case you forget your password. You will also select a User Name and a Password that will be required to gain access to portions of our site. We use the Personal Information that we collect from you or from third parties for the following purposes: 
    * to enroll you as a member of the Rewards Network or a program operated by Rewards Network;
    * to administer program reward confirmations;
    * to verify your identity when you contact us or use the Rewards Network program, and to contact and to communicate with you by phone, mail or email, including, for example, through monthly e-mail newsletter, sending you a welcome email confirming your membership or other general customer communications;
    * to answer your questions about the Rewards Network, your application to enroll in the Rewards Network or your Rewards Network account(s) with us;
    * to manage and operate the Rewards Network, including, but not limited to, identifying purchases you have made at participating merchants (such as hotels, restaurants or retailers) and to credit your credit card or loyalty or incentive program account, as applicable;
    * to understand your preferences and interests so that we may tailor the Rewards Network services for you, including customizing web pages on our website and displaying driving directions for you;
    * to book or make a reservation with a participating merchant (such as booking a hotel room or make a dinner reservation) on your behalf;
    * to bill you for your Rewards Network membership fee (if applicable); and
    * to comply with and obey any laws and regulations applicable to our business.
  * Email Addresses: We collect email addresses in several ways. You can provide us with your email address on our website, by sending an email to our Internet services group, by calling our call center, or by sending us a letter.
  * E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from us, but only if your computer supports such capabilities.
  * Marketing Communications: We may, with your consent, send certain marketing communications to you, including our e-mail newsletters, by e-mail or ordinary mail or contact you over the telephone with respect to products and services other than those you initially requested we provide to you. We will provide you with the opportunity and ability to tell us that you do not wish to receive such marketing communications in the future. For example, if you do not want to receive our dining e-mail newsletters, or other dining e-mail marketing communications from us, you may unsubscribe or opt-out from such dining marketing communications by clicking the link included at the bottom of each e-mail message we send to you. Please read the section entitled "Reviewing, Changing Your Information or Unsubscribing" for details on how to unsubscribe from other forms of marketing communications we may use.

##### When and With Whom We Share Your Personal Information

We will not sell or rent your Personal Information to any third parties under any circumstances, except in connection with a sale of all or part of our business. We will share your Personal Information within our corporate group (meaning Rewards Network Inc. and its affiliates) in connection with the purposes outlined above and with our partners only as discussed at the beginning of this Privacy Policy; but aside from this, Rewards Network Inc. will not share your Personal Information with any other third party unless we have your express permission, except under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required or permitted by law.

We may from time to time send special offers to you on behalf of our partners which we think may be of interest to you. We will provide you with the opportunity and ability to tell us that you do not wish to receive such marketing communications in the future.

We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners and participating merchants. We may also sell aggregated demographic and statistical information to our partners, participating merchants, suppliers of our participating merchants and other third parties. None of this aggregate demographic or statistical information is linked to any Personal Information that can identify any individual person.

##### "Email a Friend" and "Refer a Friend" Information

You may use our Email a Friend service to send restaurant links to family and friends via email. Rewards Network will automatically send a one-time email inviting your family and friends to visit the specific restaurant page on rewardsnetwork.com. We store the information for the purpose of sending these emails and to measure overall response rates to these services. Your family and friends may contact us to request that their information be removed.

You may use our Refer a Friend service to refer your family and friends to become members of Rewards Network. Rewards Network will automatically send a one-time email inviting your family and friends to visit rewardsnetwork.com and become members of our program. We store the information for the purpose of sending these emails, to measure overall response rates, and to accurately credit your account for each referral that signs up for a membership. Your family and friends may contact us to request that their information be removed.

##### How we use Cookies

We use cookies on our website to collect session data for several purposes, such as to personalize and improve your individual viewing experiences on our site. Cookies placed on your computer by www.rewardsnetwork.com can only be read by the www.rewardsnetwork.com web server. We use two different types of cookies in our web site:

  * "Session cookies" track the user's progression through our sites in a single visit. These cookies enable us to remember things as the user progresses from one page to another. Your session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your browser. In addition, if you leave your browser open for a prolonged period, they are set to automatically erase themselves after a short period.
  * "Persistent cookies" remember a user at the user's next visit to our web site. Your persistent cookies are not automatically erased, and they remain on your computer until you erase them. (If you do not want these cookies to remain on your computer, you can erase them by following the steps for your specific browser: Internet Explorer or Netscape.) For members, we use a persistent cookie to remember your User Name, name, and preferred dining area.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit.

##### Third Party Cookies

Rewards Network is currently using and has contracted with Omniture Inc. ("Omniture"), a third party, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers to administer our web site in order to constantly improve the web site quality. All data collected by Omniture on our behalf is owned and used solely by us.

To accomplish this, Omniture uses cookie technology to help track summarized visitor behavior. Omniture sets cookies on our behalf, which will be listed under the domain 2O7.net. You can opt-out of Omniture tracking by visiting http://www.Omniture.com/privacy/optout.html.

##### Details on Clear GIFS

What are Clear Gifs?  
Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information.

##### How We Use Clear Gifs

To help us improve visitor experience and manage site content, third party vendors and our site utilize clear gifs to track visitor behavior.

##### Links to/from Other Sites

Our web site may have links to other sites on the Internet that are owned by third parties ("External Sites"), or you may come to our web site from a link on an External Site. These other web sites will have their own rules on privacy that you should review. Rewards Network is not responsible for the privacy policies of External Sites.

##### Data Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you. We are constantly enhancing our security measures.

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that encrypts information and keeps the data private and confidential between your machine and www.rewardsnetwork.com. This technology makes it safer to transmit your credit card number over the Internet. Look for two security icons, the "s" after "http" in the address line and the lock in the top menu bar and bottom status bar of your browser in Netscape (or in the bottom status bar only in Internet Explorer).

##### Reviewing, Changing Your Information or Unsubscribing

At any time you can correct or update your Personal Information, or unsubscribe, opt-out or modify your preferences pertaining to our newsletter and other marketing communications (whether made by e-mail, telephone or ordinary mail). To review, change or update your Personal Information, or unsubscribe or opt-out from our monthly newsletters or other marketing communications, you have several options:  

  * On the www.rewardsnetwork.com site login to your account and click on the "My Account" link at the top of the home page. Then click on the appropriate link to change your Personal Information or modify your newsletter subscription or marketing communication preferences.
  * By e-mail. Unsubscribe or opt-out from our email newsletter or other marketing communications by sending an email request to [customerservice@rewardsnetwork.com](mailto:customerservice@rewardsnetwork.com). For your security, please do not email credit card changes.
  * By postal mail. Please include your email address and mail your request to us at Rewards Network Inc., P.O. Box 619400, Miami, FL 33261-9400, Attention: Member Services.
  * By phone. Call toll-free at 1-877-491-3463 (8am - midnight ET, 7 days a week.)
  * Link to unsubscribe. Links to unsubscribe or opt-out from future newsletters and other marketing communications are included at the bottom of each email.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to this information or making corrections.

Requests to be unsubscribed or to opt-out from marketing communications will be processed immediately, however you may be included in the selection for additional newsletters and communications for up to 1 week. Delays may occur if the email address or postal address information you provide us does not match the information in our database.

##### Our Privacy Officer

We have appointed the following person to be responsible for ensuring that the protection of your Personal Information is carried out in accordance with our Privacy Policy:  
Mr. Bryan R. Adel  
Senior Vice President, General Counsel, Secretary and Privacy Officer  
Two North Riverside Plaza, Suite 950  
Chicago, Illinois 60606  
Phone: 312-521-6767  
Fax: 312-521-6768  
Email: badel@rewardsnetwork.com  

##### Notice of Changes

This Privacy Policy was created on July 28, 2004. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time without prior notice. At any time, you may visit our website to view the current policy.

If our Personal Information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes prior to their effectiveness. If you are unsatisfied with our privacy policy at any time, you may discontinue participation in the program. If you are concerned about how your Personal Information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically to view any changes in this Privacy Policy.

##### AFFILIATES

Rewards Network Establishment Services Inc.  
Rewards Network Services Inc.  
Rewards Network International, Inc.  
Rewards Network Canada GP Corp.  
Rewards Network Canada LP  
TMNI International Inc.  
RTR Funding LLC  
iDine Media Group Inc.  
FFA Acquisition Corp.
